oogle.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy - Oogle

This privacy policy sets out how OOGLE.COM uses and protects any information that you filled when you visited our website.

OOGLE.COM is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Whenever we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in agreement with this privacy statement.

**SCOPE**

This Privacy Policy describes the personal information that OOGLE.COM may collect from you. Your personal information which includes, your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities, individuals or third parties for commercial, contest or advertisement purposes

All information will ONLY be used to update you about OOGLE.COM products and services that might interest you.

**_IP Address:_** An IP address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you have access to our systems, we may view the IP address of the gadget you use to connect to those products. We use this information to determine the location of the device and to determine the number of devices simultaneously accessing the product.

**COOKIES**

What are cookies? Cookies are small text files that are fixed on your browser by websites that you visit. We use cookies on our website to enhance user experience and to make our site work efficiently, for example, to save your preferences for the duration of your visit, and also to help us identify product features in which you may have the greatest interest.

_**How to Manage Cookies** :_ Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. To find out more about cookies and how to control and manage them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all functions of the website.

**HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Product development and improvement: We may use the personal information we collect about you to ask you to participate in surveys to improve our products. Besides, we may use the information, combined in aggregate form with the personal information we have collected about other users of our professional financial and media products, to plan and implement developments of, and enhancements to, our products and product range.

**SECURITY**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personal information you provide to us.

We will never request for your Credit Card details and we advice you not to enter it in any forms

**YOUR PRIVACY**

Your privacy is important to us at _OOGLE.COM._ To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. You agree to agree to these policies by virtue of using our website in a way that leads to you providing us with personal information.

**YOUR CHOICES**

You may contact us to access the personal information you provide to us and to ask us to update, correct, or delete it from our databases. You may also request that we cease using your personal information for marketing purposes. If you do not wish to receive marketing emails, newsletters and marketing materials from OOGLE.COM about the products and services we provide, or if any of your contact details are incorrect, please let us know by contacting us via email.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

This Privacy Statement may be updated periodically. We will indicate below when it was most recently updated and inform you, in this Privacy Statement, through email, newsletter and a notice on the appropriate OOGLE.COM of any significant changes.

###### Privacy Policy Last Updated May 1st, 2017.
